<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Caffeinated Brad</title>
    <link>http://www.caffeinatedbrad.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Caffeinated Brad</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <managingEditor>caffeinatedbrad@gmail.com (Bradley Jones)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>caffeinatedbrad@gmail.com (Bradley Jones)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 11:02:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.caffeinatedbrad.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Isolating VPN Traffic By Running VPNC In A Container</title>
      <link>http://www.caffeinatedbrad.com/post/isolating-vpn-traffic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 11:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>caffeinatedbrad@gmail.com (Bradley Jones)</author>
      <guid>http://www.caffeinatedbrad.com/post/isolating-vpn-traffic/</guid>
      <description>Why would you want to do this? For me there are two reasons:
 When I&amp;rsquo;m connected to a VPN (It&amp;rsquo;s usually for work) I don&amp;rsquo;t want all my traffic being slowed down. Updating local system packages and downloading ISOs end up taking up to 10 times longer which depresses me because I can&amp;rsquo;t max out that 200Mbs down connection I pay for!
 As mentioned in my previous post when I&amp;rsquo;m doing development on the go I&amp;rsquo;m using a Raspberry Pi as an Access Point and to actually do work on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portable Raspberry Pi Dev Box</title>
      <link>http://www.caffeinatedbrad.com/post/portable-raspberry-pi-dev-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 18:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>caffeinatedbrad@gmail.com (Bradley Jones)</author>
      <guid>http://www.caffeinatedbrad.com/post/portable-raspberry-pi-dev-box/</guid>
      <description>Portable Pi   For sometime, I&amp;rsquo;ve been interested in the idea of doing &amp;lsquo;real&amp;rsquo; work from mobile devices. As a software developer and self proclaimed command line junkie, having access to a real terminal on the go is essential to my work. There are terminal emulators available for both iOS and Android but they aren&amp;rsquo;t exactly productivity tools as they lack package managers etc.
This for me is where a Raspberry Pi comes in, a small, compact device that can be run off a reasonably sized battery pack for a good few hours (I&amp;rsquo;ve got around 5-6 hours from a small 5200Mah battery).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenStack Summit Vancouver</title>
      <link>http://www.caffeinatedbrad.com/post/curvature-presentation-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2015 02:46:42 +0100</pubDate>
      <author>caffeinatedbrad@gmail.com (Bradley Jones)</author>
      <guid>http://www.caffeinatedbrad.com/post/curvature-presentation-update/</guid>
      <description>I was fortunate enough to spend the last week at the 6-monthly OpenStack summit in Vancouver, Canada. Lots of buzz around the conference as usual, these summits just keep getting bigger and bigger.
Most of my time was spent in the container(docker) talks but I did get a chance in one of the Horizon developer sessions to give a short update on the Curvature work, presentation here.
Difficult not to come back from these conferences full of motivation and excitement, going to be a really good release with lots of great changes coming!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get WebEx working in Linux</title>
      <link>http://www.caffeinatedbrad.com/post/get-webex-working-in-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 18:13:27 +0100</pubDate>
      <author>caffeinatedbrad@gmail.com (Bradley Jones)</author>
      <guid>http://www.caffeinatedbrad.com/post/get-webex-working-in-linux/</guid>
      <description>Unfortunately getting WebEx running under Linux isn&amp;rsquo;t as simple as OS X or Windows where you can just download the browser plugin. Linux is listed on the WebEx support page although there are a couple of limitations and missing features:
 Can only view webcams not broadcast your own No way of specifying audio (capture/playback) devices through the WebEx UI which makes using USB microphones slightly trickier but there is a work around (see below) Only supports 32-bit Firefox and Java  Getting 32-bit Firefox and Java Obviously if you&amp;rsquo;re running a 32-bit OS then you can just install Firefox and Java using your favourite package manager.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>